3host.com 2017-02-23

# 3Host - Free Adult Web Hosting

**Privacy Policy**

_**I. Welcome**_

3Host.com is proud to be the home of a adult webmaster community in cyberspace.

This privacy policy applies to the web sites, or networks, owned by 3Host.com, ("The 3Host Network").

Even though The 3Host Network provides a different combination of services, this policy states the company-wide Privacy Policy with regard to data collection practices. 

By visiting The 3Host Network, becoming a registered member of any of the sites, you hereby provide your consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy, and are aware that our policy may change over time as discussed below. Specifically, this Privacy Policy may be updated to reflect new features, services and options, and any changes on the use of personal information. Continued use of  The 3Host Network and its services will indicate that you agree with any changes. 

Your privacy on the Internet is incredibly important to The 3Host Network and should also be to you too! The 3Host Network collects certain information about its visitors and members. The 3Host Network feels that you should fully understand the terms and conditions that deal with that collection and use of information. This privacy statement discloses what information we collect, how we use it, and how to correct or change it. 

_**II. Nature of Information Collected**_

There are two types of information collected by The Sultr yServer Network core site: (A) anonymous and (B) personally identifiable. The 3Host Network's collection practices regarding these two are discussed in greater detail below. 

**A. Anonymous Information Collection**

Anonymous information refers to information that cannot be tied back to a specific individual. As with visiting any web site, The 3Host Network collects some basic information about your computer, including browser type, operating system, IP address, Internet service provider and geographic location. 

**B. Personally Identifiable Information** **  
**  
Personally identifiable information can be used to directly identify an individual. The 3Host Network requires a limited amount of personal information to be collected in order to better serve you. This allows 3Host to set up your e-mail account and give you free web page space. 

_**III. Use of Cookies**_

The 3Host Network uses cookies on the join and login pages. A cookie is simply a small data file sent to your computer by The 3Host Network that identifies your computer as a unique user to a specific web site. It also collects anonymous information and tracks traffic patterns. A cookie will not provide any personally identifiable information about you, nor will it read data off of your hard drive, or read cookie files created by other web sites. The 3Host Network uses the information provided by a cookie for tracking site usage and targeting of advertising. This allows The 3Host Network to customize your visit and save you time during subsequent visits. 

By visiting any of  The 3Host Network sites and/or registering to become a member, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

The 3Host Network places advertising on our sites that originates from third party advertisers and/or advertising agencies. In some cases, if you click on or view these ads, the advertiser may assign you a cookie. The 3Host Network does not control these cookies. 

_**IV. Purposes for Which Information is Collected**_

The 3Host Network tracks anonymous information to determine which pages are preferred based on traffic to those areas. This information is aggregated to provide The 3Host Network with demographic and other statistical data that allows us to assess how well our web site is performing. This helps us to continue building a better service for you. The 3Host Network does not track what individual users read, only the performance of each page overall. 

The personal information collected from our members, or anyone that submits their personal information, is also used for the administration of our site; including corresponding with our members by e-mail when required and setting the content of web site.. 

The 3Host Network compiles statistical data on the number of visitors who access the banners and advertisements on our web site so that we can provide marketing information to our advertisers and sponsors. The 3Host Network aggregates this information and creates statistical reports from the anonymous and demographic information for our advertisers. This allows our advertisers to advertise more effectively, and allows our users to receive advertisements that are pertinent to their interests and needs. Also, because The 3Host Network derives their revenue mainly from advertising, providing this data is essential to maintaining our services as free to users. 

_**IV. Sharing of Information Collected by The 3Host Network**_

The 3Host Network shares anonymous data collected from visitors and citizens with third party advertisers and advertising agencies so that they may target their advertising and provide better services. The 3Host Network does not, however, disclose any personal information to these third parties without first obtaining your consent. 

The 3Host Network will cooperate, as appropriate, with police, judicial and other law enforcement agencies and disclose personal information and data upon receipt of the appropriate court orders. The 3Host Network will also share personal information where it appears that, based on sufficient evidence, a visitor or a member is engaged, through the use of or access to this web site and its services, in illegal activities. The 3Host Network refers citizens to The 3Host Network's Terms of Use. The 3Host Network reserves the right in the absence of a court order, to release information concerning a citizen who The 3Host Network believe is in violation of the guidelines or is using The 3Host Network's servers for illegal activities. 

_**V. Collection of Data by Third Parties**_

This web site contains links to other web sites. When accessing the web sites of third parties advertising on The 3Host Network, including through ad banners and other links, you will be accessing sites that are not operated or controlled by The 3Host Network. These sites may collect anonymous and personal information by various methods, including the use of cookies. The privacy policies of these web sites may not be the same as those of The 3Host Network and may not afford visitors and citizens the same level of protection. Visitors and citizens should contact these advertisers to verify the privacy policies of these web sites and their terms of use when accessing them and prior to providing any anonymous or personal information. 

_**VI. Export of Data**_

The 3Host Network may export information collected from visitors and members to countries or territories other than the country of residence of the visitors and citizens (including countries that do not necessarily afford by law the same amount of protection to personal information as the country of residence). The 3Host Network complies with the laws and/or policies that protect a country's citizens from any dissemination of exported data to third parties without prior consent. 

_**VII. Chat Rooms and Message Boards**_

The 3Host Network does not monitor their chat rooms or message boards. You are advised to consult the guidelines in the Chat and Message Board Rules. When engaging in chat rooms and message boards, you may be invited by third parties to provide your own personal information. That information could be used by third parties for purposes that you do not wish they be used, including unsolicited e-mails and sharing of personal information with other third parties. The 3Host Network strongly suggests that you do not share any of your personal information with third parties in chat rooms or message boards. 

_**VIII. Storage and Security**_

Data collected by The 3Host Network is stored in secure servers located in New Jersey. The 3Host Network has security procedures in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under its control. These security measures include the necessary protection to prevent, as far as possible, access to The 3Host Network databases to parties other than The 3Host Network. 

_**IX. Review, Correction of Information and Deactivation of Citizenship**_

Members and anyone who has submitted personal information may, at any time, review the information relating to them contained in The 3Host Network's databases and edit any incorrect information. 

A member may decide at any time to terminate his/her membership with The 3Host Network. If so, a member should contact The 3Host Network using the contact information provided to request the termination and deletion of any personal information already collected by The 3Host Network. Please be advised that because of backups, and records of deletions, it may be impossible to delete all information about a member without some residual information still remaining. 

All requests to review, edit, or terminate a citizenship will be processed by The 3Host Network within a reasonable time of their receipt. 

_**X. Protection of Minors**_

The protection of children's online privacy is very important to The 3Host Network. For that reason, it is our policy not to collect or maintain information at our web sites from those we actually know are under 18 and no part of our web sites is structured to attract anyone under 18. 

_**XI. Consent, Opt-In and Opt-Out**_

Visitors and members of The 3Host Network confirm by visiting any of the sites or the submission of their personal information that they consent to the collection and processing of personal information, the use of cookies and transfer of personal data in countries other than their country of residence as detailed above. 

Should a member at any time wish to withdraw his/her consent and opt-out of receiving communications from The 3Host Network, the member should inform The 3Host Network by following the procedures set out in the Review, Correction of Information and Deactivation of Citizenship section. 

|
